export const riddlesList = [
    {
        id: 0,
        riddleQuestion: 'I have pages but I’m not a tree, and in me you can find lots of knowledge. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Book',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'You can read me and find me in a library.',
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        riddleQuestion: 'I swing in trees, I love bananas. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Monkey',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'A playful animal that lives in the jungle.',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        riddleQuestion: 'I’m not alive, but I grow. I don’t have lungs, but I need air. If I drink, I die. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Fire',
        isDeadEnd: true,
        hint: 'It can warm you up or burn things down.',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        riddleQuestion: 'I’m always in front of you, but you can never see me. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Future',
        isDeadEnd: true,
        hint: 'It hasn’t happened yet, but it’s always coming.',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        riddleQuestion: 'I can fill a room but take up no space. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Light',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'You turn something on to make me appear.',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        riddleQuestion: 'The more of me there is, the less you see. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Darkness',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'I come when there is no light.',
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        riddleQuestion: 'I have keys but no locks. I have space but no room. You can enter but not go outside. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Keyboard',
        isDeadEnd: true,
        hint: 'You use me to type on a computer.',
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        riddleQuestion: 'I go up but never come down. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Age',
        isDeadEnd: true,
        hint: 'Everyone has it, and it increases every birthday.',
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        riddleQuestion: 'I always move forward but never backward. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Time',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'You see me on a clock, and I never stop.',
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        riddleQuestion: 'I’m a digital world, vast and diverse. What am I?',
        riddleAnswer: 'Decentraland',
        isDeadEnd: false,
        hint: 'A metaverse where you can buy land using MANA.',
    },
];
